TOHO CO . , LΤD .
A TOHO EIZO PRODUCTION
It 's hot . Hurry !
Okay !
Nice wind !
- Here . - Thanks .
Summer vacation is almost here .
I envy you , Gorgeous . Your fabulous dad has a villa .
But you 're going to a training camp with the others , Fantasy .
Yes , but I wish you 'd come with us .
It 'II be boring .
Don 't be greedy , Fantasy . Your love , Mr. Togo , is going too .
Hey , that 's mean , Gorgeous . You call yourself my best friend ?
Let 's go .
Hey , Fantasy .
Why were you staring at me ?
Because you looked like a witch in a horror movie .
You really did .
You are fantastic as usual .
You 're mean . No photos for you then .
Fine .
How 's the picture ?
- Teacher . - Summer vacation is almost here .
I 'm going to KaruiZawa with my dad .
I see . Is your father doing well ?
Yes . He 'Il be back from Italy tomorrow .
That 's great . And you ?
My friends and I are going to Mr. Togo 's sister 's inn .
Fine .
- Congratulations . - What ?
We heard you 're getting married .
- Who told you ? - Mr. Togo .
What 's he like ?
I bet you 're getting married for love .
naturally .
It 's an arranged marriage . Now go to class .
Yes , ma 'am !
How nice .
Summer vacation .
Wait , Fantasy !
- I 'II give you the photos . - AII right .
Hey , wait up !
Hello !
- Bye-bye . - Bye .
Gorgeous !
Bye-bye !
Daddy !
- welcome back . - welcome back !
I expected you tomorrow .
How was the movie job in italy ?
Leone said my music was better than Morricone 's .
You 've grown .
- You too . - Hey , watch it .
Souvenir ?
I want to talk .
Yes ?
Summer vacation is starting in a week .
Daddy .
Don 't tell me we can 't go to KaruiZawa .
We can . Sure .
Then what is it ?
We 've got a companion .
Who ? He or she ?
Come out , will you ?
Gorgeous , Iet 's shake hands .
hello .
You mean her ?
This is Ryoko Ema .
- You 're beautiful . - Thank you .
You 're charming when you smile .
Let 's be friends .
I hope you two will get along .
She 's going to be your mom .
My mom ?
I wanted to tell you earlier .
She 's a jewelry designer .
She 's surprisingly good at cooking , and other things too .
You won 't have to mend my shirts anymore .
How 's the sleeve ?
You shouldn 't have said " surprisingly . "
It 's caught in the sweater .
Listen .
It 's been eight years since your mother died .
It 's about time we had a home again .
I won 't go with you .
Wait !
I 'm back , Mom .
Dad 's disappointed us , Mom .
He cried when I won at the sports meet .
I 'Il bully Dad .
I hate him .
The three of us together !
In a bridal costume ...
Mom .
I wonder how Auntie is .
Let 's sit down .
How nice !
The six of us vacationing by the sea !
But Gorgeous is going to KaruiZawa with her dad .
I wish she could come .
You must be happy to be with Mr. Togo for 1 0 days !
Of course , melody . He 's so manly and handsome !
What ? Our teacher is manly ?
You 're so cool , Kung Fu !
She 's more manly than he is .
Keisuke Togo .
If there 's anything cool about him , it 's his name . Right , Prof ?
Stop teasing her . She 's a dreamer , that 's her asset .
- Sorry , Fantasy . - That 's okay , Sweet .
He 's not so bad .
Hey , you guys , I hope his sister is a good cook .
You want to get fatter , Mac ?
Don 't make me hit you !
Stop it . We 'II have a fun time at the training camp .
Listen to you ! You sound like a coach .
Gorgeous !
- Morning ! - Is your dad back ?
Your dad is the best .
He 's a film composer and rich !
No ! He 's the worst .
Good morning .
Mr. Togo !
Bad news .
My sister is going to have a baby .
- What ? - So ...
her inn won 't be open this summer .
I 'm sorry .
Does that mean we can 't go to the training camp ?
Right .
- That 's awful ! - Do something !
Yeah ! It 's your fault !
Don 't bully him !
There you go , Fantasy !
She 's right .
Don 't bully me .
Isn 't that a pistil and stamen ? - What ?
Quiet , everyone !
- What is it ? - Come with me .
To KaruiZawa ?
With your dad ?
No . To my mom 's hometown .
To my aunt 's house .
That 's how I invited them to your house , Auntie .
Forgive my sudden letter . I realize I only met you once .
I hope you don 't think I 'm strange .
I 'm in such a mood . I feel like crying .
I want to see my mom 's hometown again
and spend time with you like I did with her .
Please write back that I can visit you .
Cute kitty !
Where are you from ?
Gorgeous !
Bye-bye !
What is it , BIanche ? Come on .
You 're welcome to come .
Your aunt has been waiting for your letter for years .
Come see me .
Come to my house , Gorgeous .
I 'm sorry . You took time off for nothing .
That 's all right .
Maybe we can just go without her .
Don 't worry about it .
After all , I spoiled her .
- I have an idea . - An idea ?
I 'll go to her aunt 's house later .
I want to talk to her alone .
It 'll be all right .
This is my first trial in becoming her mother .
I promise ...
I 'II bring her back ,
her wonderful ,
mysterious smile .
Thanks , Ryoko .
I need some time to think things over ...
in the countryside .
Auntie !
Morning .
Good morning .
Good morning , Mr. Painter !
Bonjour , monsieur .
The bucket 's stuck !
It 's 8 : 00 already .
Where 's Gorgeous and Mr. Togo ?
hello , Mr. Togo ?
What 's keeping you ? Fantasy 's been crying .
We 're gonna miss the train .
It 's not serious , but I have to go to the hospital first .
What ? No more buses today ?
AII right , then , I 'II take my car . Bye .
He 'II come later .
What about Gorgeous ?
Maybe she 's already inside the station .
Take care !
- She isn 't here . - She must be .
- But - - Maybe she 's in the train .
There she is !
Gorgeous !
You 're late . We were worried .
Sorry . I 've been looking for Blanche .
Who 's Blanche ?
Come on , Mac !
Wait !
chocolate , candy , bread , love and dreams !
These are our seats .
Blanche !
There you are .
- So this is Blanche ? - Cute !
" The train runs through town , white dreams on board ,
speeding into the landscape ... "
A rainbow !
- It 's only 1 0 : 00 . - " Over the rainbow " !
Your appetite amazes me , Mac .
It means I 'm healthy .
You can 't imagine the pangs of hunger I feel .
You know something ?
Any old cat can open a door .
Only a witch cat can close a door .
tell me about your hometown .
What 's your aunt like ?
She and my mom loved each other very much .
My mom took me there once when I was six .
I haven 't seen her since .
1 941 , THE WAR CONTINUES ... A long time ago , Japan was in a big war .
A long time ago , Japan was in a big war .
This is Auntie 's house .
Her late father was a doctor .
This is my grandma .
This is my mom . Isn 't she cute ?
She looks like you .
My aunt and her fiance .
He 's handsome !
He was going to run the hospital .
You mean they didn 't get married ?
No , because of the war .
That looks delicious !
THE FOLLOWING YEAR Is food all you think about ?
Is food all you think about ?
- A draft card . - Not a housekeeping book ?
A pinky promise . They 're making a promise .
I promise I 'LL COME BACK !
I 'LL WAIT FOREVER - " l 'll wait up for you " ? - lt says " forever " there .
- " l 'll wait up for you " ? - lt says " forever " there .
- It 's burning ! - A kiss of fire !
- Men were more manly back then . - They were !
Kung Fu is more manly than they are !
She 's not seeing him off ?
It 's too painful for her .
I feel sad .
He 's so serious .
He 's manly .
They 've been shot !
THE WAR ENDS
The war ended , but my aunt 's fiance never returned .
OH , NO ! The war ended , but my aunt 's fiance never returned .
But she 's still waiting .
How romantic !
FIVE YEARS LATER , PEACE RETURNS It 's wonderful .
It 's wonderful .
My mom 's wedding .
all in white .
I 'Il wear it at my wedding too .
- You think you can find a groom ? - Yes , I do !
So beautiful !
I wonder how Auntie is doing .
It 's like a cotton candy !
Since my grandma died , she 's been living alone .
She gives piano lessons to the neighbors .
- My mom told me so . - Wow ! Piano ?
This is our stop .
SATOYAMA VILLAGE
- Which way ? - I forgot .
I 'm going that way . Bye !
really , which way ?
- That way ! - That way it is .
- Let 's go . - Come on , Blanche !
RETURN TO THE COUNTRYSIDE GET married
Blanche is leading the way .
- melody ! - Come on .
MELODY - Melody ! - Come on .
- Fantasy ! - Okay .
FANT ASY - Fantasy ! - Okay .
- So many trees ! - Prof !
PROF - So many trees ! - Prof !
PROF - Sweet ! - I 'm scared .
- Sweet ! - I 'm scared .
SWEET - Sweet ! - I 'm scared .
KUNG FU I feel energized .
A healthy appetite !
MAC A healthy appetite !
Gorgeous !
GORGEOUS Gorgeous !
I 'm scared , Prof. It 's spooky .
What are you saying ? Ghosts don 't exist .
Chicken ! Leave the ghosts to me .
This is so tasty .
hello !
What a landscape !
We 're lost in another world .
Don 't scare me !
Don 't be silly .
Let 's ask here .
- hello ! - Anybody around ?
Watermelon ! Can I have one ?
No , Mac !
Come here , girls .
Where 's the house ?
The mansion ?
My aunt 's .
Are you the lady 's niece ?
I thought so .
You look like her . especially your eyes .
That 's it . The house .
Look !
Let 's go !
Thank you .
Come on !
We haven 't had visitors for long time .
I 'm sure ...
the lady will be very pleased .
There it is !
She 's right .
What a place !
It 's huge !
This house is something , isn 't it , melody ?
Huh ?
hello !
You 've got a telegram .
We 've got a patient , Doctor .
- Open sesame . - Oh , Kung Fu !
Gorgeous is so stylish !
Putting on makeup ?
Blanche ?
Welcome .
Auntie !
All seven of you together . How lovely .
hello !
How you 've grown . You look just like your mother .
When did we last meet ?
It was Grandma 's funeral .
Ten years ago . - It 's been that long ?
AII this time , I 've been waiting for you only .
I 'm sorry .
I hear you teach piano .
I used to .
But not now . I 'm alone .
What happened to your legs ?
Don 't worry . I have you now. I 'm all right .
I 'll take a picture .
- please join us . - Come on , everyone .
Say cheese !
- Butter ! - Margarine !
- Jam ! - Sexy !
I 'm sorry about your camera .
But don 't look so sad .
I 'm really happy that you 've all come to visit .
Smile .
Hey !
Look !
What a watermelon !
It 's a gift for you . Doesn 't it look good ?
Oh , no , you didn 't -
- Did you sneak it away ? - You 're greedy !
I paid for it .
It 's as fat as Mac !
Come in , everyone .
It 's cool in here .
Come on , Melody . Your shoes .
Do I take my shoes off ?
Oh , you .
Dear chandelier , shine on them !
will you close the door ?
One , two , three , push !
well done ! You 're so cool , Kung Fu .
You like piano ?
Yes , very much .
There 's a grand piano in the other room .
Take a look .
This cat 's eating a lizard .
I 'll clean the house .
I know you 're tidy , but this house is too big for you .
- We 'II help her . - Thank you .
It 's Melody .
Auntie 's piano .
What a big room !
What 's over there ?
It looks like a clinic .
melody !
This is her bedroom .
It 's wonderful . - Isn 't it ?
There are so many pictures of the cat .
What is it ?
A skeleton .
Her grandpa used to treat patients in this room .
Don 't startle me .
Then I taught piano here .
It was long ago .
The village was prosperous and full of people .
Even girls from town came here to take lessons .
Auntie ,
you don 't have visitors anymore ? - No .
I get hungry whenever I 'm startled .
I want to eat .
Mac !
AII right .
But the trouble is
I can 't work much in the kitchen .
Don 't worry . We 'II cook .
really ? Thank you .
You must 've been lonely .
Yes , I 've been lonely .
But now I have many young girls in my house .
I 'm glad .
AII right . Let 's split up the jobs .
We know who 'll do the cooking .
You 're right . That 's for me .
I 'lI do the cleaning . Do you have a broom ?
It 's in there .
Where 's the kitchen ? I want to put this away .
I 'II take you there .
I 'Il go too .
It 's a big clock .
Where is it ?
Here we are .
Some kitchen !
Isn 't it ?
The young lady will warm you , dear stove .
" Dear stove ? "
Cooking stove .
What 's that ?
A stove is a stove .
I 've been living alone ,
so I talk with the furniture and equipment as I work .
Dear fridge , may I cool this in you ?
It 's out of order .
How about a natural refrigerator ?
You mean a well ?
wonderful !
It 's over there .
So it 's been decided .
I 'll assume leadership till Mr. Togo comes .
AII right .
I 'll go to the kitchen .
Don 't karate-chop any dishes .
help , Kung Fu .
Step aside .
Awesome !
What ? It 's just a mouse .
- Cute ! - There 's another one .
I remember this well .
The water is cold , so it 'll be nice and chilled .
How nice !
help me with this .
One , two ...
What if we lose it ?
Don 't worry , Mac . people always used to do this .
That 's a funny nickname for a girl .
She 's a big eater . She 's like one big stomach .
So we call her Mac .
Shut up !
Mac , you sure look tasty , being round and all .
How can you say that ?
I 'm so hungry that I 'm about to pass out .
She was joking . Let 's make supper .
- I 'II get the bath ready . - How lively she is .
- Auntie . - Yes ?
Why do you wear glasses outdoors ?
The bright sunlight frightens me .
It 's the spitting image .
- Maybe she came out of the picture . - ridiculous !
You 're fantastic , Fantasy .
Hush ! We 'lI wake Auntie up .
Don 't worry . She was in the sun too long .
Without supper , she 'II be hungry .
She 's not Iike you , Mac .
- One , two , three ... - What are you doing ?
- Beauty stretch ? - Toilet ?
- Need help with the watermelon ? - l 'll be fine .
Mac , your ribbon .
Thanks .
You 're pretty without glasses , Prof.
Really ?
But without them , I can 't see a thing .
Oh , that 's just too bad !
Let 's finish up .
- Then we 'lI play . - Let 's play hide-and-seek .
Mac 's still gone .
She just left .
But the well is right behind the house .
Why don 't you look for her ?
She does imagine things .
Mac !
What a beautiful sunset !
Where is she ?
She didn 't get it yet .
How beautiful !
Mac ?
Fantasy .
Tasty !
- What 's wrong ? - Are you all right ?
You 're muddy .
- " Hearts in the Mud " ? - hold yourself together .
- What 's the matter ? - What happened ?
Auntie ! Aren 't you sick ?
It 's so noisy .
The head !
A human head !
Everybody has one .
A decapitated human head !
Decapitated ?
In the -
ln the well !
I 'll take a look .
You can walk ?
You gave me energy .
Let me go .
Let 's go to the well .
Are you all right , Fantasy ?
Oh , poor girl .
A watermelon .
is this a head ?
It 's well chilled .
She fooled us .
Fantasy .
You 're imagining things again .
Stop it . I 'll clean the house .
There 's a potato field down the road .
I bet Mac went there .
She loves baked potatoes .
Maybe she 's playing hide-and-seek .
She 's impossible . I 'II take a look .
I 'll save you some watermelon .
Save a big piece for Mac .
Fantasy .
I 'm really sweaty . Let 's take a bath .
Not before the others .
It 's all right .
She 's our sponsor .
I 'm sorry , Sweet .
Don 't be . I Iike cleaning .
- Wait . - What ?
Where 's the bedding ?
Over there .
Where on earth did Mac go ?
Don 't worry . She 'lI come back .
Without eating the watermelon ?
I 'm thirsty .
Where can she be ?
You opened the door ?
Where is the bedding ?
Sweet .
I Iike the countryside .
How 's the bath ?
Fine .
I need more water to wash my hair .
AII right . You 're a stylish princess .
Time to work .
An illusion ?
The cicadas are so noisy !
I wonder where Mac is .
This is ridiculous .
Maybe it was an illusion .
Sweet ?
You 're in a good mood .
When I was a child , I went to a restaurant in town .
I was excited like I am now .
Don 't worry , Fantasy .
You 'II see Mac .
Excuse me .
Not again !
You broke it !
She -
She went in the fridge !
You 're imagining things again .
See ?
I 've been lonely .
This song ...
Melody .
You 're welcome to come .
Your aunt has been waiting for your letter for years .
Come see me .
Come to my house , Gorgeous .
Auntie ?
Blanche !
Any old cat can open a door .
Only a witch cat can close a door .
melody ?
That 's melody !
Let 's go !
- Help ! - The piano room !
That 's Sweet .
Sweet !
You 'II feel no pain !
You have interesting fingerprints .
It 's only a scratch . Don 't scream like a kid .
Sorry .
But it felt as if the piano bit me .
The piano ?
You sound like Fantasy .
Kung Fu ! Prof ! It 's terrible !
Not again .
Sweet , the mattress !
- Is she sleeping ? - No ! Come with me !
- shall we go ? - all right .
- Where ? - There .
Sweet ?
- What 's this ? - Mattresses everywhere !
Fantasy !
That 's melody ! Something 's wrong again .
- Go to her . - No , I can 't go alone .
You must !
melody ?
Fantasy .
toilet paper , please .
Sweet 's apron .
And her bra !
What the -
Was she stripping here ?
What are you doing ?
She didn 't have to vanish , even if she stripped .
What are you doing here , BIanche ?
The doll 's stripped too .
I found her panties .
- Something smells funny . - Yeah , it smells .
I saw it .
The mats and sheets Ieaping on her like beasts .
That 's not logical .
She must be taking a bath .
probably . I 'II go check .
Mac 's gone too .
All of us will disappear . I 'm sure of it .
- What do we do ? - Don 't worry .
Your love , Mr. Togo , is coming soon .
He 's a man , after all . He can help us .
He 'II be the knight in shining armor come to save the damsel in distress .
Oh , my lovely Princess Fantasy !
Help me , Mr. Togo !
My lovely teacher !
I helped you ! I love you !
" End " - No . " The end " !
- Strange . She 's not there . - See , I was right .
Wait .
Gorgeous was taking a bath .
Come to think of it , where is she ?
I bet she 's putting on makeup as usual .
- She must be upstairs . - Let 's go .
- What about us ? - Let 's follow them .
This way ?
She always takes her time .
She 's playing hide-and-seek .
Gorgeous ?
- She isn 't here . - Ready or not -
Here we come .
She stripped too ?
- Oh ? - Gorgeous ?
I can see you !
We were worried sick about you .
I don 't blame Fantasy . I understand .
Mr. Togo is coming soon . Be patient .
- Mr. Togo ? - In an old buggy .
But he acts like he 's flying a plane .
A plane ?
Nothing .
Don 't worry .
We 'II call the police in the village .
Let 's see .
Wait . I 'II call them .
- Help me ! - Get over here now !
- Help ! - Come here now !
What 's wrong ?
It 's out of order .
- Where are you going ? - The police station .
I 'll bring help .
Leaving us alone ?
In this creepy house ?
Why be scared ? Her aunt is here .
I 'll be back .
Take me with you !
- I want to go too . - Me too .
Stay here till I come back .
Take me !
The door won 't open .
Strange .
follow me !
- Oh , no ! - We 're trapped !
Let 's put on silk dresses
Together , you and me
Let 's go out
To the dance hall
I can still hear
That beautiful song
My silver shoes are taking steps
To that beautiful song
Hey ! Get that toy car of yours off the road !
Sorry . But the traffic 's so heavy .
I 'm sorry .
Got that ?
I 'm scared .
It 's like a horror movie .
That 's out of date .
- Step aside . - So this is a karate movie !
- Stop it . There 's no use . - Why not ?
There must be some kind of device .
Device ?
Auntie lives alone .
So the doors must close automatically at night .
could she do that ?
That 's right .
She graduated from a music school in Tokyo .
She 's educated .
Oh , yeah ?
- I have an idea . - What ?
Ask her how to open them .
I see !
Auntie ?
There 's a human hand in here .
What ?
That 's Mac 's ribbon .
Maybe -
Maybe what ?
Nothing .
Melody , play the piano to cheer us up .
No. I 'm scared .
Please .
That 's a good idea .
Hey , don 't touch my butt !
Well , all right .
ShouIdn 't Gorgeous be back by now ?
Things are going just as Fantasy imagined .
But too many strange things are happening one after another .
What are you thinking , Prof ?
I can 't tell you .
Why ?
Because I 'm not completely sure of it yet .
Besides , Fantasy would pass out .
What ?
That 's Gorgeous !
You 're right . When did she come back ?
- Gorgeous ! - Let 's go .
Come on .
No ! I 'll stay here . You too , Melody ?
Let 's go .
Gorgeous ?
Look at me , Melody .
Turn around , Melody !
My fingers are gone .
Oh , my ! That 's naughty .
What 's this ?
" Lonely Days . "
Gorgeous ?
Give me the light .
It 's unscientific , unexplainable , unnatural , unreasonable .
It doesn 't make sense .
You 're so cool , Kung Fu !
I 'm sorry , Sweet .
Kung Fu ?
lmpossible !
I can 't believe it !
Can such things happen in this world ?
What 'lI we do ?
My knees are wobbling .
Fantasy !
melody !
Come on ! Wake up !
Fantasy ! Come on !
Wake up !
You must be brave now .
Drink .
melody .
You were right . This is a haunted house .
- What the - - goldfish .
Even Gorgeous is a ghost now .
No ! all lies !
Even if you don 't believe me , we have to cooperate .
That 's the only way to survive .
Good noodles !
Thanks a lot .
AII right ! I 'm ready to eat .
Thanks , Pop .
We 'lI meet again someday , somewhere .
Bye !
- Wait ! - This is so good .
Hurry ! We need to build a barricade .
" There are no young girls in the village anymore .
I 'm all alone .
But I 'II keep waiting for him in this house .
He wasn 't killed in the war .
I know he 'II come back .
Because he promised . "
- What 's going on ? - Fantasy .
What 's the matter , Gorgeous ?
I 'm -
I 'm in my aunt 's world .
Her world ?
Huge lips !
She died many years ago .
- She died ? - That 's right .
Then who was it we met ?
She wanted to be married so badly
that her body remained alive after her death .
And she eats all the unmarried girls who come here .
That 's the only time she can wear her bridal gown .
Now it 's your turn .
Just let me eat you .
Gorgeous !
Come on , brace yourself !
Spare us !
We were your friends !
It 's no use . She 's not the Gorgeous we knew .
help , Gorgeous !
Fantasy !
God , help us !
What now ?
Damn it ! I won 't give in !
Don 't leave us !
- I 'Il phone for help . - l 'm scared !
She said it was out of order . She said so .
It 's a lie .
Wait !
Just leave it to me .
police ? Help !
Help me now !
Let me out of here !
Gorgeous - Come on , ghost !
There are no houses at all .
" l 'll be waiting here with Blanche in my arms .
With Blanche , in this house "
Blanche !
Kung Fu ! The cat ! Destroy it !
Kung Fu ! Don 't lose ! Go !
Mac ...
Sweet ...
Melody ...
Kung Fu ...
We did it !
The diary !
" I know he 'lI come back .
Because he promised .
He promised he would . I 'lI wait . "
Look , Prof !
The cat 's blood !
" With Blanche in my arms . "
Mr. Togo !
Maybe he isn 't coming .
Why not ? He promised .
No , he didn 't .
He promised me !
But he didn 't promise Auntie or the house .
He didn 't promise the house .
You know where the house is ?
The girls were ...
eaten .
They were eaten !
delicious .
- Do you like watermelons ? - No !
- What , then ? - Bananas .
Banana ! Banana !
Bananas everywhere !
" Gorgeous wrote to me .
A young girl is visiting me again .
I 'II send blanche for her . "
The cat ?
My glasses ! I can 't see .
Prof !
Blanche .
Gorgeous !
It wasn 't true .
You aren 't a ghost .
I 'm glad .
Gorgeous !
Fantasy .
Fantasy . - Gorgeous .
It 's not true ! tell me it 's not true !
Gorgeous ...
I want to sleep .
Mommy .
Just at a glance
You fell in love
With the view of the sunrise
From this window
It 's still dark
At the flower garden
But butterflies will be flying over
They 'll be here soon
Why don 't you move in to this house
As my wife
Let 's start a new life
Together , you and me
hello ?
Without love
Sunrise will never come
Anybody here ?
hello ?
Anybody ?
I touch your body
With my hand
Bedtime comes
Even for chirping birds
Gorgeous !
Good morning .
Gorgeous .
Come in .
Thank you .
I 'm glad .
Thank you for coming .
Where are your friends ?
still sleeping ?
But -
They 'II get up soon .
They 'lI be hungry .
They wake up
when they 're hungry .
Gorgeous !
Even after the flesh perishes ,
one can live in the hearts of others
together with the feelings one has for them .
Therefore ,
the story of love must be told many times
so that the spirits of lovers may live forever .
Forever .
The one thing that never perishes ...
the only promise ...
is love .
STARRING
KlMIKO IKEGAMI
MlKI JlNBO , KUMlKO OBA Al MATSUBARA
MIEKO SATO , ERIKO TANAKA MASAYO MIYAKO
KlYOHlKO OZAKI SAHO SASAZAWA
ASEl KOBAYASHI MlTOSHl lSHlGAMI
TOMOKAZU MlURA FUMl DAN , GODlEGO
HARUKO WANlBUCHI
YOKO MINAMlDA
Concept by CHlGUMI OBAYASHI
Screenplay by CHlHO KATSURA
Cinematography by YOSHlTAKA SAKAMOTO
Production design by KAZUO SATSUYA
Music by ASEl KOBAYASHI and mickle YOSHlNO
Songs performed by GODIEGO
Directed by NOBUHIKO OBAYASHI